- id: k-hyogai-3005
  prompt: "Meanings: repeater, iteration mark (のま)\nUsage: Repeats the preceding kanji"
  answers:
    - 々
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-hyogai-5446
  prompt: "Meanings: be amazed, disgusted, shocked\nOnyomi: ホウ\nKunyomi: ほけ.る, ぼ.ける, あき.れる, おろか"
  answers:
    - 呆
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-hyogai-53e9
  prompt: "Meanings: strike, beat, hit, thrash, criticize\nOnyomi: コウ\nKunyomi: たた.く, はた.く"
  answers:
    - 叩
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-hyogai-53f1
  prompt: "Meanings: scold, reprove\nOnyomi: シツ, シチ\nKunyomi: しか.る"
  answers:
    - 叱
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-hyogai-54b3
  prompt: "Meanings: cough, clear throat\nOnyomi: カイ, ガイ\nKunyomi: せ.く, しわぶ.く, せき"
  answers:
    - 咳
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-hyogai-5618
  prompt: "Meanings: lie, falsehood\nOnyomi: キョ, コ\nKunyomi: うそ, ふ.く"
  answers:
    - 嘘
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-hyogai-565b
  prompt: "Meanings: chew, bite, gnaw\nOnyomi: コウ, ゴウ\nKunyomi: か.む, か.じる"
  answers:
    - 噛
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-hyogai-589f
  prompt: "Meanings: ruins\nOnyomi: キョ\nKunyomi: あと"
  answers:
    - 墟
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-hyogai-5c41
  prompt: "Meanings: fart, passing gas\nOnyomi: ヒ\nKunyomi: へ"
  answers:
    - 屁
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-hyogai-7092
  prompt: "Meanings: broil, parch, roast, fry\nOnyomi: ソウ, ショウ\nKunyomi: い.る, いた.める"
  answers:
    - 炒
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-hyogai-72d0
  prompt: "Meanings: fox\nOnyomi: コ\nKunyomi: きつね"
  answers:
    - 狐
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-hyogai-75d2
  prompt: "Meanings: itchy\nOnyomi: ヨウ\nKunyomi: かゆ.がる, かゆ.い"
  answers:
    - 痒
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-hyogai-7e4b
  prompt: "Meanings: tie, fasten, chain, tether, connect\nOnyomi: ケイ\nKunyomi: つな.ぐ, かか.る, か.ける"
  answers:
    - 繋
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-hyogai-8210
  prompt: "Meanings: lick, lap up, taste, underrate, despise\nOnyomi: シ\nKunyomi: ねぶ.る, な.める"
  answers:
    - 舐
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-hyogai-8d05
  prompt: "Meanings: luxury, extravagant\nOnyomi: ゼイ, セイ\nKunyomi: いぼ"
  answers:
    - 贅
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-hyogai-91a4
  prompt: "Meanings: a kind of miso, soy sauce\nOnyomi: ショウ\nKunyomi: ひしお"
  answers:
    - 醤
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-hyogai-98f4
  prompt: "Meanings: rice jelly, candy\nOnyomi: イ, シ\nKunyomi: あめ, やしな.う"
  answers:
    - 飴
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-hyogai-9bad
  prompt: "Meanings: salmon\nOnyomi: カイ, ケイ\nKunyomi: さけ, しゃけ"
  answers:
    - 鮭
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-hyogai-9c10
  prompt: "Meanings: alligator, crocodile\nOnyomi: ガク\nKunyomi: わに"
  answers:
    - 鰐
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []
